Hi, in this lesson, I want to talk with you about payment plans and some usage limitations.
So, the good news you can start using wind source of 3 with some monthly limits.
And of course, if you want to use more extensive features, you can choose one of the plans
they suggest.
Let's start with the 3 plan.
We will have about 25 credits per month and they say it's equivalent to 100 problems to
GPT 4.1.
And because each of the problems cost 0.5 to 25 credits, so it's some approximate understanding
of how much problems you can send.
Also, they provide the ability to buy some additional credits in some paid plans, but not
appropriate plan.
Starting from a 3 plan, you can use premium models, like GPT 4.1 or 4 mini clothes
on that, and Jamie and I at 2.5 row, deep seeker one and others.
But these be aware that you have really a small amount of credits.
And your first request will use the premium models until you run out of credits.
So, if you want to use different models, or you want to leave the premium models for
some different tasks, so please change immediately your model you're going to use because
you will lose all your credits.
They have features, the good news the top completions is unlimited and peruse as well.
And you have ability to deploy your application once per day for 3 plan.
It will be deployed as not run the human integration with Netlify, and so you can easily
deploy it.
And also you will help to weak a problem, so you will have 100 credits, for this 3L, and
you will have 10 deploys per app, 10 up deploys per day.
Yeah.
Let's talk about problem.
It costs 15 dollars per month, you will have 500 credits per month, so it's much bigger
amount.
And if you need additional credits, you can buy minimum quarter of 250 credits for 10
dollars.
And you can do still 10 deploy per day.
Let's talk about the team plan, can be good for you to have a team of developers, and you
want to have some centralized billions, some dashboard with analytics, priority support,
some knowledge base, so you can buy a business as a security feature, so some security
will gain, so if you really need it.
How much it costs, 30 dollars per month per user?
Every user will have 500 credits per month.
And you can buy additional minimum quarter of 1000 credits for 40 dollars, so price
same, but just the quarter bigger, and all these credits will be used across your team.
Like you buy it for all your team.
Now let's talk about enterprise plan, it costs about 60 dollars per month per user.
If you have up to 100 users, but if you have more users, you can request some special
price, so we just need to come back to winter.
Every user will have 1000 credits per month, and additional credits will cost 60 dollars
per 1000 credits.
Some of the credits will be put between all members in your team.
You will have some additional features, like role-based access control, same as a
solid, you will be included, and you shouldn't pay for it for enterprise plan.
They also mention in the documentation you will have highest priority support and longer
model context plans, but on different pages they provide different information, so it's
better if you clarify this information.
What else?
If your organization has more than 200 users, you can get some discounts, any discounts,
so it's nice news.
You have also dedicated account management and some hybrid deployment option.
Okay, let's now talk about models usage.
The user prompt credits when you send a message to cascade, cascade is a chart interface,
with a premium AI model.
Each model uses a different number of credits.
One message usually cost about one credit, and you can see all models and their prices
on a model's page.
I will show you right now.
So when you run out of credits, the premium models will stop working, but you can still
use some free models.
So let's check what models they have.
You will find the slim kind of resources for this lesson, and I will click show all models.
As you see, they have some, their own winter models.
If you scroll down, you will see their own models for the foreign engineering tasks, so
you can check what is the difference.
Yeah, and you see these models are free.
Okay, some of the models, this one model is available for limited time, and they might
disable it later.
So here you will see the list of models, the cost of credits, how much they cost.
You will see also the plans, and for every plan, they will show what models are supported.
Also, you have the BYO key.
So what is it?
If you scroll down, you can see that you can bring the own key, and then you will use the
API.
The API, the pricing is different, it's a bit cheaper, so if you enter, so you can also
use this option.
And if you see, let's check, for example, the O3 high reasoning model cost about one
credit, the Gemini 2.5 per all, a bit less, and you see it's also from a pricing, limited
number of times, quotes on that, cost one credit, so that's syncing cost a bit bigger.
For example, O4 mini cost 0.25, it's also some from a pricing for now, a GPT for all cost
one credit, a lot for opus, okay, you can use only by your API keys, they're not provided
by default, a deep seek with three cost zero credit, so you can use it for free, and you
can use for free, the own model light version.
What else?
A growth cost one credit, and the mini one costs really cheap.
So Gemini 2.5, you can see the prices, oh, it's really a big variety of models you can
use, and opus was useful for you and now you know what plan it's better to see it for
you and what models you will use, and see you in the next lessons.